# CHRISTOPHER NOHALL

FRONT END SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

#### INFO

#### PHONE

+86 176 8553 7870

#### **EMAIL**

christopher.nohall@gmail.com

#### SKILLS

Experienced Speaker

 $\bullet$   $\bullet$   $\bullet$   $\circ$ 

Pedagogical

 $\bullet$   $\bullet$   $\bullet$   $\circ$ 

Complex Problem Solving

 $\bullet$   $\bullet$   $\bullet$   $\circ$ 

Interpreting

• • • 0 0

### LANGUAGES

Swedish

• • • • •

English

....

Chinese

 $\bullet$   $\bullet$   $\bullet$   $\circ$ 

Korean

• • 0 0 0

### **PROFILE**

Dedicated programmer with several years of experience effectively working on completing the tasks and projects at hand. Bringing forth a lifelong passion for solving problems, combined wit a curiosity to learn new concepts. Adept in building positive relationships with workmates and clients. I am committed to bringing my best to each project.

### **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

## Front End Developer, Nohall Solutions

Jeju-Si, Republic of Korea

Oct 2016 - Present

The biggest project I worked on was for OnCourse Technologies. The project spanned over two years. I worked on writing code that analyzed 3D-models and recognized different features. The part was analyzed to see if it was possible to create with CNC or casting and what the cost would be. The customer was shown a visualization of the part with the different features and a quote. The project was mostly based JavaScript but I also worked with Three.js, Node, Git, C#, TypeScript and webpack.

### English Teacher, a Chinese Middle-School

Qingdao, China

Jul 2015 - Jun 2016

### EDUCATION

### Royal Institute of Technology

Stockholm, Sweden

Aug 2009 - Jun 2010

Studied Maths, Physics and Engineering

### Dalarnas Högskola

Jul 2013 — Jun 2015

Studied Chinese Linguistics, Business and Culture

### REFERENCES

### References available upon request